{"sid": "PT6D9Y5XKNI7_main", "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 435115, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 435116, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["calc_1", 445002], ["calc_6", 445734], ["calc_+", 446471], ["calc_7", 447242], ["calc_8", 447757], ["calc_6", 448416], ["calc_=", 449220], ["submit", 453572]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "282", "answered_time": 453572, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "282", "question_time_start": 453572, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["calc_7", 457852], ["calc_6", 458535], ["calc_+", 459040], ["calc_4", 459723], ["calc_7", 460252], ["calc_=", 461068], ["submit", 464834]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "271", "answered_time": 464834, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "271", "question_time_start": 464834, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["calc_3", 468334], ["calc_+", 468939], ["calc_7", 469968], ["calc_9", 470668], ["calc_+", 471472], ["calc_8", 472184], ["calc_8", 472309], ["calc_=", 473250], ["submit", 477217]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "258", "answered_time": 477217, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "258", "question_time_start": 477217, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 483606]], "time_left_end": "252", "answered_time": 483606, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "252", "question_time_start": 483606, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 492227]], "time_left_end": "243", "answered_time": 492227, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "243", "question_time_start": 492228, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 498571]], "time_left_end": "237", "answered_time": 498571, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "237", "question_time_start": 498571, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 516223]], "time_left_end": "219", "answered_time": 516223, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "219", "question_time_start": 516224, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 520855]], "time_left_end": "215", "answered_time": 520855, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "215", "question_time_start": 520856, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 527136]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 527136, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 527137, "question": "6+6+59", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 534667]], "time_left_end": "201", "answered_time": 534667, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 534668, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "201", "question_time_start": 534668, "question": "8+3+9+24", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 543255]], "time_left_end": "192", "answered_time": 543255, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "192", "question_time_start": 543255, "question": "9+3+8+87", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 553621]], "time_left_end": "182", "answered_time": 553621, "user_answer": "107", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "182", "question_time_start": 553621, "question": "46+59", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["calc_4", 557972], ["calc_6", 558699], ["calc_+", 559334], ["calc_5", 560055], ["calc_9", 560783], ["calc_=", 561633], ["submit", 565631]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "170", "answered_time": 565631, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "170", "question_time_start": 565632, "question": "3+53+96", "correct_answer": 152, "events": [["calc_3", 569493], ["calc_+", 570349], ["calc_5", 571166], ["calc_3", 571688], ["calc_+", 572349], ["calc_9", 573055], ["calc_6", 573554], ["calc_=", 574286], ["submit", 578725]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "157", "answered_time": 578725, "user_answer": "152", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "157", "question_time_start": 578725, "question": "6+3+66", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 588770]], "time_left_end": "147", "answered_time": 588770, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "147", "question_time_start": 588771, "question": "97+48", "correct_answer": 145, "events": [["calc_9", 591842], ["calc_7", 592389], ["calc_+", 593283], ["calc_4", 593900], ["calc_8", 594487], ["calc_=", 595275], ["submit", 598566]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 598566, "user_answer": "145", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 598567, "question": "4+8+4+58", "correct_answer": 74, "events": [["calc_1", 603908], ["calc_6", 604559], ["calc_+", 605132], ["calc_5", 605774], ["calc_8", 606321], ["calc_=", 607015], ["submit", 610391]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 610391, "user_answer": "74", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 610391, "question": "3+14+37", "correct_answer": 54, "events": [["submit", 615883]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 615883, "user_answer": "54", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 615883, "question": "27+844", "correct_answer": 871, "events": [["calc_2", 625337], ["calc_7", 625932], ["calc_+", 626608], ["calc_8", 627283], ["calc_4", 627903], ["calc_4", 628049], ["calc_=", 628715], ["submit", 632483]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "103", "answered_time": 632483, "user_answer": "871", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "103", "question_time_start": 632485, "question": "7+8+49", "correct_answer": 64, "events": [["calc_7", 637118], ["calc_+", 637715], ["calc_8", 638252], ["calc_+", 638840], ["calc_4", 639507], ["calc_9", 640049], ["calc_=", 640682], ["submit", 643834]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "92", "answered_time": 643834, "user_answer": "64", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 643834, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "92", "question_time_start": 643834, "question": "4+8+7+29", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["calc_1", 649375], ["calc_9", 650935], ["calc_+", 651586], ["calc_2", 652265], ["calc_9", 652932], ["calc_=", 653699], ["submit", 656983]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "79", "answered_time": 656983, "user_answer": "48", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "79", "question_time_start": 656984, "question": "6+8+9+78", "correct_answer": 101, "events": [["calc_6", 663135], ["calc_+", 663582], ["calc_8", 664215], ["calc_+", 664965], ["calc_9", 665692], ["calc_+", 666319], ["calc_7", 667047], ["calc_8", 668153], ["calc_=", 668838], ["submit", 672671]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "63", "answered_time": 672671, "user_answer": "101", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "63", "question_time_start": 672672, "question": "19+83", "correct_answer": 102, "events": [["submit", 681816]], "time_left_end": "54", "answered_time": 681816, "user_answer": "103", "user_correct": "False", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "54", "question_time_start": 681817, "question": "9+7+58", "correct_answer": 74, "events": [["calc_1", 692348], ["calc_6", 692915], ["calc_+", 693463], ["calc_5", 694014], ["calc_8", 694508], ["calc_=", 695198], ["submit", 699064]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "37", "answered_time": 699064, "user_answer": "74", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "37", "question_time_start": 699064, "question": "66+226", "correct_answer": 292, "events": [["calc_6", 704537], ["calc_6", 704683], ["calc_+", 705365], ["calc_2", 706105], ["calc_6", 706668], ["calc_6", 706820], ["calc_C", 716414], ["calc_6", 718365], ["calc_6", 718524], ["calc_+", 719119], ["calc_2", 719834], ["calc_2", 720031], ["calc_6", 720598], ["calc_=", 721258], ["submit", 725696]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "10", "answered_time": 725696, "user_answer": "292", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "10", "question_time_start": 725697, "question": "3+9+7+28", "correct_answer": 47, "events": [["submit", 731997]], "time_left_end": "4", "answered_time": 731997, "user_answer": "47", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "4", "question_time_start": 731998, "question": "6+24+29", "correct_answer": 59, "events": []}}}}}